Guide to the album 'A Trip in Algeria' by TAYLOR, H. E. Irving AD.MC.040
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- The inside back cover of the album 'A Trip in Algeria' containing a company mark from M. W. & Co. Ltd. London., Circa December 1901 – April 1902; AD_MC_040_ref57; Taylor, H.E. Irving; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_040)
  London, England, UK; Algeria; English Writing; Advertisements
- The back cover of the album 'A Trip in Algeria'., Circa December 1901 – April 1902; AD_MC_040_ref58; Taylor, H.E. Irving; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_040)
- The spine of the album 'A Trip in Algeria'., Circa December 1901 – April 1902; AD_MC_040_ref59; Taylor, H.E. Irving; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_040)